But why him, of all people?
What was Father thinking, giving that man
of unknown lineage the Black Blade?
It was from when Father was an adventurer.
He pushed into
the deepest corner of the Dungeon
of the Lost with the Sovereign Six.
It was a long and dangerous quest
that yielded a prime dungeon relic.
That blade is made of
an unknown material,
harder than mythril,
orichalcum, and mana-metal.
No matter the technique or skill used,
nothing will cause even a scratch on it.
It's otherwise known as
the "Unbreakable Blade."
The biggest question is, how has such
a resilient material gotten so beat up?
That sword has value
beyond that of a weapon.
To casually just let that sword go...
No...
I'm thinking about this wrong.
Father has also noticed the sense
of unrest hanging over this country.
In all likelihood,
Father is counting on that man.
That man who defeated a minotaur
and saved Lynne's life.
He can be a secret weapon
for a "something"
that will happen in the future.
Actually, Lynne...
Is it okay for you to be seen out here?
Yes. Right now, I am first
and foremost an adventurer.
Oh, okay.
I'm thinking of going to
the guild after eating.
Sounds good, Instructor Noor!
Oh, man.
I'm really not someone who should be
considered an instructor,
but the more I try to
clear up the misunderstanding
the more complicated this situation gets.
And she's following me everywhere
like it's a normal thing to do.
I'll get some work from the guild,
and eventually she'll be able to grasp
how simple of a person I am.
I hope you find a good task, Instructor!
Let's eat!
Noor...
Why are you with Lady Lynneburg?
Master.
As an adventurer, my name is Lynne.
No need to add any titles.
Oh, my apologies, Lynne.
What's all this?
Something happen again yesterday?
Uh, well...
It's really difficult to explain.
It's fine, one of the rules here
is to not stick your nose
in other people's business.
Forget I asked.
Uh, but I wanted
to get some advice though...
So, what brings you here today?
Looking for work?
Uh, yeah.
One two people can do, if possible.
A two-person job, huh?
I believe you're a silver B-rank, Lynne?
Yes.
If you two form a party,
you can at least take on
the goblin hunting job
in the outskirts of the capital.
G-gob...
Goblin hunting?!
Goblins are those monsters that
adventurers the world over use
to put their skills to the test!
Sir, can we really take on that task?!
Yeah.
Lynne can accept silver tasks on her own,
but bringing along a partner with
a lower rank than hers is a liability.
Normally, the job
drops down a rank or two.
Will this work out?
A quest outside the castle!
Whoa, wait...
Doesn't this mean I'm taking
advantage of Lynne's adventurer rank?!
And to think,
up until now all I wanted
was for her to go back home
as soon as possible.
She sees right through me!
How self-absorbed of me.
I'm ashamed!
Would Lynne seriously
form a party with me?
What's wrong?
U-um, are you okay with this?
I mean, I'm relying on your rank
to take this job.
Of course I'm okay with it!
If there's anything I can do for you,
Instructor, just say the word!
R-really?
I feel pitiful depending on
such a young girl for this.
But still...
one of my dreams is coming true!
Then let's head out.
Wait!
I haven't told you
where you're going or anything!
Oh, right.
So you're gonna take this one, yeah?
Yes, please.
Don't push yourself too hard.
A low threat level
doesn't mean you'll be safe.
I know what my limits are.
You're going to this area.
Only report what you've caught.
That's the Forest of Beasts, isn't it?
Correct.
The right ear will be
the proof of your successful hunt.
You can't get compensated without it,
so make sure you bring it back with you.
The right ear, got it.
Well, there've been reports lately of
their numbers decreasing by a good amount,
so if not one of them shows itself,
pick some medicinal herbs or something
and bring those back.
Right.
Okay, get on with it.
And I'm serious,
be careful not to get hurt.
We're off!
Open up!
Let's get to it, Lynne.
Sure thing, Instructor!
So this is the Forest of Beasts, huh?
The trees are pretty dense here.
These are a different type of tree than
the kind I see in the southern forests.
They're huge!
The ecology is a little different here
than in other places.
Oh, is it?
Lynne, what kind of creatures are goblins?
Huh?
I mean, I'd like to
hear about them beforehand.
Uh, right!
Normally, they hunt small animals
as prey and eat the fruits off the trees,
but they've been aggressively
attacking humans for sustenance too.
If we leave them be their numbers may grow
too much it could lead to a food shortage,
and then they could overflow
into human villages.
That's why adventurers
are regularly hunting them
and controlling their numbers.
Controlling them...
It's said that the abundance
of the ecological system of the forest
depends on whether or not
there are goblins there,
so it's not good to hunt them
to extinction either.
Actually, this forest also has
rare flora and fauna you can see
that are not found in other places,
so it's also used as a training ground
and a place to gain income
for beginner adventurers.
Good to know.
Not only does Lynne have the skills,
but she also has extensive knowledge.
There's hardly anything I can teach her...
What about here?
None here either.
How about that...
Under normal circumstances,
we would have already encountered them.
It seems the rumors about
the goblin numbers dwindling are true.
Oh, there's a response
from a monster-like thing.
It's a little far, though.
For real?
Yes.
Doesn't seem like it'll take much time
to get there, so let's go take a look.
It keeps getting darker.
There are a lot of very old trees
around this part,
and it's hard for the sun
to shine through.
Goblins seem to prefer a place like this.
Oh, okay.
What?
What's wrong?
The presence of a monster was up ahead...
but it's disappeared.
It's gone?
Yes.
Monsters are living things, too.
Can't they die from illness or old age?
That is definitely a possibility...
Around here!
There's... nothing there.
Looks that way.
No, wait.
What is that?
Uncover!
Huh?!
What is that?
It's a goblin...
That's a goblin?!
It's way bigger than I imagined!
They're said to be the weakest,
but there's a huge difference
in hearing about it
and having one right in front of you!
But those features check out.
Green skin, walking on two legs,
piercing, beast-like eyes!
And they use tools!
Do all adventurers handle these guys
like they're nothing?!
Of course she's freaked out.
Although she's blessed with abilities,
she still has very little
actual combat experience.
There's nothing to be scared of, Lynne.
We're only up against a goblin.
Terrifying.
But I can't think about that!
We're gonna take it down!
Right, Instructor!
Uncover!
Huh?!
That's the... Goblin Em-
The Goblin Emperor!
A subspecies of the Goblin King
that is considered an extreme threat!
The Goblin Emperor is a monster created
from genetic manipulation by man.
The deviant research that brought forth
this forbidden knowledge is now banned!
On top of that,
this one eats its own kind,
then ingests that power
and grows stronger!
There's nothing to be scared of, Lynne.
We're only up against a goblin.
I don't believe it!
Did he come here because he sensed it?!
The reason he acted so excited
to take on this job
was because he wanted to eliminate
this threat no one knew about!
We're gonna take it down!
That's right, I'm not alone right now!
Right, Instructor!
Parry!
Trying to corner me?
I'm not gonna let that happen!
Parry!
Lynne!
Okay!
Windcutter!
Icicle Dance!
I can't hit him!
I didn't think it could be so quick!
Parry!
Instructor!
Are you all right?
In front of you!
Parry! Parry!
I have to do something...
Huh?!
Where's the wound?!
Even Goblin Emperors
shouldn't be able to recover that easily!
What's that?
Instructor!
The mana-stone on its forehead!
If you can get that off,
we just might beat it!
No way, was he watching
how many I could parry?
I can't block them all!
Windblast!
Are you okay?
You're a lifesaver!
It's just as I thought!
It's constantly replenishing
its power with the mana-stone.
At this rate, we're just going
to run out of stamina and magic!
But, if your magic attacks can't hit him,
then nothing I can do will work!
Lynne, can you aim that at my back?
Aim it to...
You mean Windblast?!
Yes.
That move is powerful enough
to demolish castle walls!
No matter how strong you are,
Instructor, it-
It won't hit me directly.
This sword can withstand it.
I think the only chance we've got
is to go faster than him!
Okay!
Here I go!
You can do it!
Windblast!
Physical Enhancement!
Featherstep!
My body!
Low Heal!
Instructor!
Where's the mana-stone?
Right here.
Lynne, will you finish it off?
I'm sorry, but can you make sure
it doesn't suffer much?
All right.
Hell Flare!
I'm sorry, goblin.
I'm gonna refrain from anymore
goblin slaying for the time being.
I shouldn't get overconfident
and go into dangerous situations.
I'll take on the next challenge
after I've trained more
and gotten stronger.
So it was a Goblin Emperor this time.
I can hardly fathom how powerful it was
with this pure of a mana-stone.
According to the reports, it was
several times the size of a Goblin King.
Yes, I see.
Something like this is abnormal.
The Magical Empire may be responsible
for the incident itself.
But this mana-stone...
We think it could be a Demon's Heart
from the Holy Theocracy of Mithra.
How is Lynne?
Only minor wounds, miraculously.
Must have been a hard battle.
It's amazing they were able
to overcome it.
The monster hid itself
behind a powerful seal
and ambushed them
in the Forest of Beasts.
Lady Lynneburg believes it had been there
for a few days, maybe more.
What?
And this seal is one such that not even
the Secret Corps can perceive it?
But how were they carrying
such a bulky thing
all the way to this country
in the first place?
If it was summoning magic,
the sensory network in the capital
should have caught it.
Were there no telltale signs
in the perimeter?
The number of goblins was decreasing,
so the adventurer's guild has been
requesting an investigation into it.
There may have been several
similar cases in other areas as well.
This report is a summary of questionable
instances from the last three months.
Well done.
Continue on with the investigation.
Well, never thought that little runt from
back then would grow up to slay goblins!
It was way harder
than I imagined it'd be.
Lynne saved the day,
and we managed to get the job done.
Oh no, that isn't true!
All the same, I should celebrate
my first day hunting.
It may be a minor thing
to other adventurers,
but to me this is a huge step forward.
Let me guess, you just watched
on the sidelines, huh?
I guess that's the wiser choice, though!
Yeah.
To be honest, I just helped out a little.
I have no idea where I'd be now
if Lynne hadn't been there.
I'M the one that only helped
YOU out a little...
Well, even goblins
are still a threat to newbies,
so it was good experience, right?
You said it.
Until I saw them in real life,
I had no idea goblins were like that,
and I hadn't even thought about the stone
on its forehead being a weak point.
A stone on the forehead?
What are you talking about?
It was a reddish color,
and a pretty stone at that...
Oh, you mean the mana-stone?
It's normally buried in the heart
or the throat, though.
You sure that was really a goblin?
I really do think it was.
Yeah!
If that's what you say it is, Instructor,
then it's a goblin.
No matter what anyone says!
Might've been a rare type, then.
Now then, show me the proof of the kill.
I'm gonna get you your cash.
The right ear.
I told you to remember to bring it back.
What's wrong?
We burnt the goblin up.
To ashes.
What?
#4 I Parry a Goblin